First of all, whatever update you got on Dylan, what happened to him, and why he could not return to the game?
首先，不管你得到关于Dylan的什么最新消息，他到底怎么了，为什么他无法回到比赛中？
I have not had an update. Just knowing he went out when he took awkward landing. I guess I don't know if he fell, but that awkward landing.
我还没有收到最新消息。只知道他在一次别扭的落地后离场了。我不确定他是否摔倒，但就是那次别扭的落地。
I just heard he wasn't coming back. I haven't got an update yet.
我只听说他不会回来了。目前还没有收到更新。
It seems pretty obvious, but down Fox, then Harper's out. What kind of pressure does that put on the rest of your backcourt in a game like this?
看起来很明显，Fox先倒下了，然后Harper也出去了。这对你们后场其他球员在这样一场比赛中带来了什么样的压力？
A ton. Obviously, this team is as good as anybody at turning you over, so when you're down some of your primary creators and initiators,
非常大的压力。显然，这支球队在迫使对手失误方面是顶尖的，所以当你们失去一些主要创造者和发起者时，
it causes a little bit of an extra strain, whether that's who to play, what to play, what to run, et cetera, et cetera.
就会造成额外的负担，无论是该让谁上场、该怎么打、该跑什么战术等等。
We'll just have to be sharper in that area because it's fully loaded against these guys.
我们只能在那个方面做得更精准，因为面对这些家伙必须全力以赴。
Obviously, 27 points off turnovers is not a winning formula.
显然，27分来自对手失误，这不是获胜的公式。
Mitch, we hadn't talked to you since the announcement about Fox pre-game.
Mitch，自从赛前宣布Fox的消息后，我们还没和你聊过。
Is that a situation where, like you said before the game, it's going to be the world you're living in now,
就像你在赛前说的，这将是你们现在要面对的现实，
but is that a situation where he could have played if you pushed him today?
但在今天的情况下，如果强行让他上场，他能打吗？
Or I guess how serious is that injury?
或者说，这伤到底有多严重？
Honestly, he's just trying to play every day.
老实说，他只是每天都在努力尝试上场。
It's a tough injury that he wouldn't be playing with in the regular season,
这是一个在常规赛他本不会带伤打的严重伤势，
so he's trying to tough it out and he did that in Minnesota and then had an awkward landing,
所以他一直在硬扛，他在明尼苏达就这么做了，然后又经历了一次别扭的落地，
and so he re-aggravated it, and we just got to make sure that he's in a place
于是伤势再次加重。我们必须确保他处于一个能够上场，
that he can be out there and compete to the level that he would need to in the game that we're playing.
并以我们比赛所需水平去竞争的状态。
And then I guess as a corollary to those two questions, Steph has been going through some turnover issues.
然后我想作为那两个问题的延伸，Steph一直有一些失误问题。
What can you do to kind of address that?
你们能做些什么来解决这个问题？
We've addressed it and will continue to just in terms of trying to help him with some of his reads,
我们已经着手处理了，并且会继续努力帮助他更好地阅读场上形势，
especially when he's tired, whether that's playing more off two feet or getting off the ball earlier with the early pass
尤其是在他疲劳的时候，无论是更多地用双脚起跳，还是更早地传球，
and just letting the ball find the open man. They do such a great job of showing crowds
让球更快地找到空位队友。他们在包夹和多人防守上做得非常好，所以不只是Steph的问题。
and the pain having multiple bodies, and so it's not just Steph.
他今晚失误确实多了，但我们全队都是。
He had too many turnovers, but our whole team did.
所以我们必须继续学会不要在那种时刻硬来，因为对手有时会逼你传球。
And so we have to continue to not fight that moment of the game where they're going to make you pass the ball at times.
在那种情况下，你必须能够和队友建立连接，
And when you have those situations, you've got to be able to connect with your teammate
因为如果你做到了，你就能从在人群中打球，变成更有可能让队友
because if you do, you go from playing in the crowd to then more than likely getting one of your teammates
在有利位置接到球——无论是追防还是空位三分。
to the basketball with an advantageous opportunity in terms of close out or catch shot threes.
即使Steph今晚有不少失误，你如何评价他的整体表现，
Even with the turnovers for Steph tonight, what did you think of his performance
以及他在今晚这种身体对抗和Thunder的强硬打法下坚持比赛的方式？
and the way he was able to play through the circumstances and the physicality that the Thunder played with tonight?
是的，他是个战士。他在场上倾尽全力。
Yeah, he's a warrior. He's out there giving it all he's got.
我认为当他没有更早传球时，他其实是错过了队友。
I think that when he doesn't pass the ball earlier, he misses a teammate.
那是因为他太有竞争力了，想要自己造机会、保持攻击性，
It's out of him being competitive and trying to make a play and be aggressive,
场上有很多事情在发生。他在和我们相处的这两年已经证明，
and there's a lot of things going on, and he's shown that in the two years that he's been with us,
他是个非常出色的传球手和创造者，我们必须继续帮助他。
he's a hell of a passer and a hell of a creator, and we've got to continue to help him.
他需要在防守端盯人，然后还要承担那么多创造任务，尤其是在没有Fox和Harper的情况下。
He's asked to guard on one end and then create that much, especially without Fox and then Harper.
这在能量输出上是非常大的负担，所以他会变得更好，
That's quite an output, energy-wise, and so it's something that he'll be better at
我们也会更好地帮助他，尽量不要给他施加那么大的压力。
and we'll be better for him to try to help him where we don't have to put maybe that much strain on him.
Mitch，你们双方球队已经有不少球员受伤倒下、离开球场。
Mitch, you got guys on both sides already banged up, going down, leaving the floor.
经过两场比赛之后，你觉得这会在多大程度上变成一场消耗战，
How much of this, after two games, do you feel like is going to be a war of attrition
考虑到两支球队的打法，以及一切都显得如此胶着？
just with the two teams, the way they play and just how tight everything seems to be?
是的，在赛季的这个阶段，每项运动似乎都是这样，对吧？
Yeah, it feels like that's always at this time of the season in every sport, right?
你必须撑到最后才能给自己机会。我认为，
You have to get to the end to give yourself a chance, and I think, again,
这就是为什么我们必须继续信任我们的轮换深度，球员们必须站出来，
that's why we have to continue to trust our depth and guys have to step up
当被叫到名字时回应号召，提供高质量的出场时间。
and when their names call to answer the bell and be able to give us some quality minutes
当你越来越疲劳、对抗强度增加、比赛激烈程度始终在线时，
and then as you do get tired and the physicality heightens and the intensity
你就必须高效执行。所以这里面既有
is ever so present, you got to execute and so there's something there
精神上、身体上还有情感上的挑战，我觉得可以这么说，
where there's a mental, a physical and emotional challenge, I guess you could say,
你必须在每一个回合的微观层面做到这一点，
and you have to be able to do that in the micro every possession
同时也要在宏观层面，在48分钟整场比赛中保持正确的心态和打法。
and then in the macro in terms of the totality of how you have a disposition
说到这个，教练，你今晚看到Jordan的表现如何？
and work a game for 48 minutes.
他算是被突然扔进了火力全开的环境中。
On that note, Coach, what did you see from Jordan tonight
你之前提到只要有机会就给他好的出场时间。
in the way that he was kind of thrown into the fire?
是的，Jordan整个赛季都在为我们这样做。
You mentioned just giving good minutes and spurts wherever you can.
他在被叫到名字时总是准备好上场。
Yeah, Jordan's done that for us all year.
他是个非常聪明的篮球运动员，知道如何执行，
He's done a great job of being ready when his name's called.
并给我们带来韧性。他今晚为我们做得很好。
Very smart basketball player, knows how to execute and give us toughness
他是个非常聪明的篮球运动员，知道如何执行，并给我们带来韧性，
and he was great for us tonight.
他今晚为我们做得非常好。